<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rev]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rev]]></description>
        <link>http://danielmrose.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 12:46:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://danielmrose.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 12:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You’re Dead To Me!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>You’re Dead To Me!</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/67092ff2-e8ab-4dc8-b67f-3a33d148170f.jpg">,<p>As a campus minister and a pastor you see a great many things. I think the hardest thing that I have had to do over years is help people see that they are in destructive relationships. Each of us has a desire to be deeply loved and accepted. For many people they are willing to be in a destructive relationship simply to be in a relationship.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/youre-dead-to-me/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">37ca028d-97ea-4012-aa02-ff64ae6dc931</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 13:23:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Death, Belief, and Jesus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Death, Belief, and Jesus</h1>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/a88ed30ce070538346b8d4713f6e9053/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=2820&cropwidth=5618&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F361486c5-b377-4754-9606-eba6b2f33aaa.jpg&x=0&y=0">,<p>Our culture does not handle death well. We are hide it. We run from it. We fight death tooth and nail. I think that there are times when we more than anything else want immortality. </p>,<p>Other cultures celebrate death. When a loved one dies they hold a parade and celebrate their freedom from this rock and their entrance into eternity. </p>,<p>Why are we afraid of it? </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/death-belief-and-jesus/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4ac07675-d3a1-4769-8226-7c62c0ab5f29</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 12:49:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Legos in the Dark]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Legos in the Dark</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3dd696cf-c819-43e4-bcc2-38a71bf59e79.jpg">,<p>As a parent of a young child there is one great fear that we all face. It is the kind of fear that strikes people to the heart. This fear is real and palpable. You might think it is the fear that comes from wondering if your child will grow up well, but it's not. Maybe this fear is that you won't like their future spouse, that's not it either.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/legos-in-the-dark/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">db9b7bf6-ddf4-4811-ac43-53b547cbaf5e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 14:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[By Faith, Not By Works]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>By Faith, Not By Works</h1>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/6211ba02a46135409ef349af545968cc/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=2212&cropwidth=3316&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F9f36dfce-6405-4397-a93e-beaa6e779c27.jpg&x=0&y=0">,<p>One of my favorite book series is&nbsp;<em>The Lord of the Rings</em>. It is an amazing tale that gets richer as the books progress. Too many times "sequels" are not as good as the original. I think what makes&nbsp;<em>The Lord of the Rings</em>&nbsp;particularly good is that it was conceived as a whole from the beginning. Many of our current novel series were not. The first one is written and published and then after it has shown to be marketable the rest of the books are commissioned. Often this leads to holes in the plot or some disjointedness in the narrative. Not so with&nbsp;<em>The Lord of The Rings.&nbsp;</em>It goes somewhere from the start. The beginning of the story really only takes its full meaning from the end of the story.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/by-faith-not-by-works/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">34cae5f5-8993-4364-baaf-fdd69f256b9a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 12:48:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Make America Great Again, Or Not]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Make America Great Again, Or Not</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/700c5d82-c8ab-4e6a-8986-a34dd77e6a31.jpg">,<p>"Make America Great Again!"</p>,<p>"We need to get back to our roots as a Christian nation!"</p>,<p>"I miss the good old days!"</p>,<p>Have you heard people say these things? Have you heard them embrace them as mantras and repeat them? Maybe you've said them too. I often wonder what people mean when they say these kinds of things. There is some sort of longing in people's hearts for our country to regain some kind of prominence that they once believed it had. Others desire to see what they consider to be a return to morality and civility.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/make-america-great-again-or-not/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5757d166-044f-422f-919e-d2d5b701cab4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 12:49:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[So Embarrasing…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>So Embarrasing…</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9c6104e0-64db-47af-a8a5-501b2e112c28.jpg">,<p>I have two teenagers right now. One of the simple pleasures I get out of being a dad is hearing, "Dad, you're so embarrassing." Yup. That's right! Typically this little phrase flies out when I am not allowing them to do something they want to do. Particularly when this happens in front of their friends. It also happens when I try to be hip and cool (this failed for me even before kids, but now it's just fun to watch them shudder). Even though I embarrass them at times, they still love me fiercely.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/so-embarrasing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03572bf2-4b6e-42df-bff8-214565cb69c8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 13:25:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Than Conquerors]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>More Than Conquerors</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d38b0463-2cdb-4051-b6b6-c84864ce04c7.jpg">,<p>I will never forget the first time I had to truly discipline Ethan. It was so hard. I cried. He cried. It was awful. Awful. When I say the first time, I mean the first time he could really understand that he was in trouble and that Dad was mad because of his actions. I think he was five or six. He was being ungrateful and so we took away his gaming system. He was able to grasp that this was something different.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/more-than-conquerors/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">802d608d-de2f-4db9-b183-af5378e859be</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 12:13:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Response to Tragedy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>A Response to Tragedy</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dec5464e-9382-4bbe-b525-aaaf124baa7b.jpg">,<p>As I have been wrestling with the tragedy that took place within our community this past week they struck me again as being timely. Maybe they will help you. Maybe they will simply come off as being trite and silly. They were cathartic for me then and they are again today. </p>,<p><strong>I wrote the following words on December 14, 2012:</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/a-response-to-tragedy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">46cc0a11-4aa8-4304-b31e-8b899e652c39</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 16:35:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Gospel is Power]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Gospel is Power</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9461b7c2-e7a4-4611-bb7c-c0d76ae978ec.jpg">,<p>What do you think of when you hear someone say, "The Gospel"? Some of us think about four point outlines or The Romans Road. Others think about service. Still others, think about the crucifixion and resurrection. Some people may think about Jesus being victorious over sin and death. You might think about how to get to heaven or how to avoid hell. Maybe you think about music.&nbsp;</p>,<p>Do you think about power?&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-gospel-is-power/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">af8da0fa-c51e-472d-a6fe-e16aa0889373</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 12:23:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eat Me]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5c93080b-aabe-489f-8c30-4609bf08e0ec.jpg">,<h1>Eat Me</h1>,<p>There are times when Jesus says things that make you scratch your head. He is one subversive dude. Jesus doesn't hesitate to say something to make a person feel uncomfortable. He shakes up the status quo. He rattles cages and doesn't even care. No, Jesus was so committed to his mission of directing folks to the Father that he didn't mind upsetting a few apple carts.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/eat-me/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7acbd2f6-56c0-4001-9d89-127e2099e279</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 13:23:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>