<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rev]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rev]]></description>
        <link>http://danielmrose.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 18:17:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://danielmrose.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 18:16:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Person of Peace]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Person of Peace</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8b11d43e-9b1c-4ac0-9cd2-4c6c917a4b64.jpg" alt="Photo by rawpixel.com on Unsplash">,<p>If the first step into the mission of God is <a href="http://danielmrose.com/show-up" title="Show Up">showing up</a>, then the second is to begin paying attention to the people around you. What are they passionate about? What are their hopes? What are their fears? What are the areas in their community that are broken? What are people worrying about? Who are the people that are trying to fix the brokenness of the world? Who are the people who know these people?</p>,<p>These people are called, “persons of peace.” In every mission setting we need to find a person of peace. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/person-of-peace/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e00dc103-835c-4dc1-aa1f-002e038467ac</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 18:13:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[He Laughs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>He Laughs</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5bbb10fe-275a-402b-8822-c1d4669b7130.jpg" alt="Photo by Christian Battaglia on Unsplash">,<p>This fall has been so much fun for me. My wife, Amy, is commuting to work every day. This means that I get to drive my daughter to dance a few times a week. Those drives are the highlight of my day. It’s amazing to get a chance to hear her heart and just to talk with her. The other she was asking me about the elections in Germany (because why wouldn’t an 8th grader be thinking about such things?). She was explaining how the German Nationalist party grew in power and how they are the descendants, politically, of the Nazis. It really bothered her. She was wondering aloud if we could see the rise of another Nazi Germany. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/he-laughs/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27115ba6-95c6-4ce9-acdb-f1b39a569a56</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 15:47:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Faith Alone]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Faith Alone</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/abc350e0-824a-4f5d-a77e-8c2967ba2144.jpg">,<p>This week, I am meditating on Ephesians 2:1-10. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/faith-alone/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">583db497-bdde-4e82-ab53-bc0aca0c3e35</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 15:35:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On The Holy Spirit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>On The Holy Spirit</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eaa44771-c8dc-4fbb-9838-0958c6b86828.jpg" alt="Photo by seth schwiet on Unsplash">,<p>*NOTE: This is the third in a series on the Evangelical Presbyterian Church’s,<em>The Essentials of our Faith</em>. Scriptural proofs can be found elsewhere. These posts will focus on the “why” and the impact of these statements in our lives.</p>,<p>I remember the day clearly. I was sitting in the office of my pastor and friend, Bob. We were discussing life and following Jesus. We were talking about the Holy Spirit. He was asking me about yielding to the Spirit and trusting him to empower me. I was not totally on board with this idea. As I shared with him that day, the thought scared me, to my core.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/on-the-holy-spirit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3881f98d-a8ba-4d3e-9408-60bce8472368</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 21:50:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show Up]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Show Up</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a7783575-3b26-4069-bbee-fcaa383d79ec.jpg" alt="Photo by Alex Jones on Unsplash">,<p>One of my favorite stories in the whole of the Scripture is the story of Saul’s conversion. It takes place in Acts 9. He’s running around trying to wipe the Church off the face of the Earth and God gets his attention. </p>,<p>That’s not the part of the story that grabs me. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/show-up/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c67e50b9-2f2f-4d4e-9efa-40b55e7e46d8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 19:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blessed Is The One Who…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Blessed Is The One Who…</h1>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/f61f807b066bacb29d07dd118ca80dfa/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3647&cropwidth=4721&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F759f0e40-e1f9-444c-bff2-1bff5694c5ba.jpg&x=0&y=0" alt="Photo by Joseph Rosales on Unsplash">,<p>We live in a time when people are always talking about how “blessed” they are. Typically that is in reference to their financial well-being. Yet, when we spend time reading the Scriptures, this image of “blessed” is not really what we see emerge.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/blessed-is-the-one-who/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c49b5681-5bcb-4ca6-97bd-6a4ba045c04b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 13:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Not Perfect]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Not Perfect</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d9b67fbf-a688-41f8-845f-bb6ba4b9f3de.jpg" alt="Photo by Daniel Tafjord on Unsplash">,<p>There’s nothing worse as a pastor when you’re having a lousy day (or few days) and you have a “weak” moment publicly. You know, one of those moments where you feel the flesh waking up. Your face heats up, your pulse quickens, your fists clench, and you know what is about to happen. You know you’re about say something you will later regret. Your mind is screaming, “NO! Stop! Run!” Your flesh is screaming out, “I will destroy. Right here, right now, I will destroy.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/not-perfect/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3585397b-e914-4bd9-b0b6-4f37f5f19e2f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 18:08:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Friend and Helper]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Friend and Helper</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/49d076cb-b7c4-461a-a835-1426c9b74817.jpg" alt="Photo by Priscilla Du Preez on Unsplash">,<p>On Wednesdays, I share what passage I’m thinking about and meditating on during the week. This week, it’s John 16:1-15. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-friend-and-helper/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9a41ceac-f2b8-45b5-8355-07337e07a49c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 18:16:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jesus is Lord]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Jesus is Lord</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/87485267-6ef9-4ab4-a8eb-9cc6e6748ae3.jpg" alt="Photo by Edwin Andrade on Unsplash">,<p>*NOTE: This is the second in a series on the Evangelical Presbyterian Church’s, <em>The Essentials of our Faith</em>. Scriptural proofs can be found elsewhere. These posts will focus on the “why” and the impact of these statements in our lives.</p>,<p>I think the argument can be made that no person in the history of the world has had as much of an impact as Jesus of Nazareth. We mark time before and after him (yes, I know that CE/BCE are the now the primary means of marking time, but they are the same as BC and AD). It is safe to say that no other person has had as much written about him or has been studied so thoroughly. His birth, life, and death have been studied, debated, and marveled at. Jesus is a name that brings a reaction in those who hear the name and in those who say the name. Regardless of your worldview, everyone must admit that this Jesus of Nazareth, was at the very least a remarkable individual. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/jesus-is-lord/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8a24b9d4-158c-495b-b175-d4e6600f2f5f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 21:26:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You Can Rest]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>You Can Rest</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e4f66147-3590-4538-83d8-6a7b8febab6a.jpg" alt="Photo by BRUNO CERVERA on Unsplash">,<p>I’ve been in full time ministry for nearly 20 years. I can’t count the number of friends who have burned out in ministry. They reach a place of complete exhaustion, desperation, hopelessness, cynicism, or depression that drives them to walk away from their calling. It’s usually some combination of these things and more. </p>,<p>There seems to be one particular trait that is cuts across all these people in their burn out. They were afraid to rest and refused to rest so they could control everything. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/you-can-rest/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e9c83cdf-72f7-4fac-b9ca-412e62bfab46</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 23:55:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>