<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rev]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rev]]></description>
        <link>http://danielmrose.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 16:49:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://danielmrose.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 16:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Jesus Way]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Jesus Way</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7a4d4657-90ab-4bbf-9ebf-2445de847e72.jpg">,<p>An insidious belief has exploded into American Christianity. This belief is that following Jesus will be all roses and puppies. Some call it the “Prosperity Gospel.” Its purveyors argue that if you have enough faith then you will have health and wealth. God wants you to be rich and that everything in your life should be going easy and well. </p>,<p>What an attractive offer! Who wouldn’t want that? </p>,<p>The problem is, that isn’t the Jesus way. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-jesus-way/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">184c9a66-b362-43f1-b2e1-4b173130494d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:20:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Lie</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8696f23d-b634-4adb-84c5-cc77698cf3b3.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-lie/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">22122e15-6d17-475f-b8c5-fd3ccad6952b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 18:47:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It Really Is About Jesus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>It Really Is About Jesus</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d4f47692-3b34-43c3-92cb-3ab8b25c9819.jpg">,<p>There is a constant refrain in our culture today, one that I have sometimes embraced, “Jesus, save me from your followers!” The Church has a bad rap because it is filled with broken people. We are all in process trying to be more like Jesus but we all fail, often. It gets really ugly when we “Jesus wash” our sinful behaviors. </p>,<p>The church functions in this world as Jesus representatives. It is completely fair for the world to, in some way, judge Jesus by the actions of the church. While it is fair, it is sad. It is sad because we fall so far short of who he is. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/it-really-is-about-jesus/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">42d1bca3-5083-49ac-b22f-3c2ce29f61db</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 15:10:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preach the Truth]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Preach the Truth</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c6365442-4316-4cfc-beb1-44b60b161f3a.jpg">,<p>In our social media world confirmation bias has become the air we breathe. If someone says something we don’t like we can “unfollow” or “unfriend.” It has become easier than ever to only hear, read, or interact with people who confirm our positions. We never need to interact with anyone who disagrees with us. Our positions or perspectives need not ever be challenged and we never need to be made to feel uncomfortable. </p>,<p>The church world is very competitive. Everyone wants to have a bigger and bigger church. Churches compete by having better facilities, cooler bands, and more dynamic programming. More and more they are finding that people will often leave when the preaching makes them feel “uncomfortable.” So, to remain competitive pastors are learning that they need to keep their sermons within a certain range of comfort to the hearers. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/preach-the-truth/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">628d6cb7-d6f9-468f-a009-7985aca16022</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 19:16:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[There’s More To It]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>There’s More To It</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/df93a531-2b6d-4670-bf17-b82613420547.jpg">,<p>One of the single hardest things about having teenage children is that they don’t see the bigger picture. They live completely in the moment and for the moment.</p>,<p>It drives me crazy!</p>,<p>We’ve all been there. It’s part of growing up. One of the hardest parts of being a parent is trying to teach your children to see more than the “now”. </p>,<p>Something the Christian has to come to grips with is not just that there’s more than the moment, but that there’s more than just this life. We must grapple with the reality of eternity.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/theres-more-to-it/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">100dcb5d-6916-47c3-b7fc-ed475545b9ba</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 18:23:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It’s Not A Sales Pitch]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>It’s Not A Sales Pitch</h1>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/9979ddb769e455aa01e61e0ebd66258e/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3263&cropwidth=3871&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F5c957430-d5b9-4c48-bed9-b2a06d1aa93e.jpg&x=0&y=0">,<p>My Dad and Father-in-law are both car salesmen. My wife, Amy, and I both grew up appreciating salesmanship. The other day I had breakfast with my Dad and he told me about his new television. He was not planning on buying a television, he just wanted to go in and buy a rack that was capable of holding his 40” TV and a 65” TV whenever he upgraded.</p>,<p>The salesman went to work.</p>,<p>Dad appreciated the salesmanship (and the price!) so he bought at new 65” TV.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/its-not-a-sales-pitch/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51e05fb6-1bc9-42a1-b1c8-8b276c6993a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 13:19:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letters of Recommendation]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Letters of Recommendation</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c98805df-f211-4b86-b173-32ed5e0c0510.jpg">,<p>In my time as a campus missionary and a pastor, I have written many letters of recommendation. I write them and then often wonder if their even read. Potential employers want them to see if this person can follow through on a mundane task or to see if a person will vouch for them.</p>,<p>In the “real” world, there doesn’t seem to be much need for letters of recommendation. Your work speaks for itself. Results matter. Your production in your field is your letter of recommendation.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/letters-of-recommendation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c8945119-2563-407d-9394-2680780b8314</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 17:27:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Christian, You Stink]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Christian, You Stink</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c0c19e28-f94b-48a8-8f25-bd0639a8c616.jpg">,<p>I really enjoy the movie <em>Top Gun</em>. I know it’s cheesy. I know it’s poorly written and the acting is average at best. It is not by any means a cinematic masterpiece. But, heaven help me, I love it.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/christian-you-stink/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c02fb717-f1c6-48c6-89f0-5a20cd46a910</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 18:46:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All The Promises]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>All The Promises</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e0c3410d-1096-434e-98a3-6e8a0b632681.jpg">,<p>When I spend time talking with friends, who are not Christians, about religion they often get frustrated with me. They get frustrated because I don’t really want to discuss things like evolution and existence of God. I’m not all that interested in those questions. I think those questions tend to work themselves out on their own in the mind and heart of a person.&nbsp;</p>,<p>What I’m really interested in talking about is not so much a&nbsp;“what” but a&nbsp;“who.” I am fascinated by the life, death, and resurrection of Jesus. Why? Because the entire faith of Christianity rises and falls on this one man. Quite simply, if he didn’t do what the New Testament writers said he did then Christianity is a complete sham and a waste of time.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/all-the-promises/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f6220778-293b-41ae-b7cc-a3e595cf3166</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 18:44:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It’s Not Just About You]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>It’s Not Just About You</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1d9d6050-f05f-4a67-af05-853325e389f3.jpg">,<p>Both of my children are teenagers. It often feels like they believe the world revolves around them. Don’t get me wrong, they are generous and kind. They care for people and I think they’re good friends. But, they are still teenagers and so at times, they believe the world revolves around them.&nbsp;</p>,<p>I remember when the full reality of my parents divorce hit me. They were divorced when I was nine but it wasn’t until later that it really sunk in. I was probably 12 or 13 and I remember thinking,&nbsp;“Why me?”&nbsp;</p>,<p>That seems to be the question we wrestle with when bad things happen to us.&nbsp;</p>,<p><em><strong>“Why me?”</strong></em></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/its-not-just-about-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1391c4df-3c4e-464a-a6cb-e7dea2877c0a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>