<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rev]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rev]]></description>
        <link>http://danielmrose.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 15:15:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://danielmrose.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 15:15:37 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forgiveness is Blessing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Forgiveness is Blessing</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/30517ac4-b294-40f6-b28f-47b21bc30dc2.jpg">,<p>I will never forget the day. I was sixteen and had had my driver's license for a few weeks. It was one of those fall days in Michigan where the leaves had fallen and there was a thick dew. My family lived in a small neighborhood shaped like a horseshoe. On my way to school I was changing CDs and not paying attention. I looked up to see I was running out of road. I slammed on the brakes and turned the car. I had hit the wet leaves and slid into a few mailboxes. Looking around, I saw no one, so I backed out and hurried off to school.</p>,<p>After school, I was watching television and the phone rang. My stomach dropped. Somehow, I knew this was about the mailboxes. I heard the "Yes" and "OK" and "We will see you soon, officer." I was dead. Mom looked at me and asked if I had been a part of a "hit and run." I was caught and all I could do was say yes and tell her the story.</p>,<p>We went to the police station where I got a scolding and then I had to apologize to the neighbors. It was horrible.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/forgiveness-is-blessing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">52cc9a5e-572c-455c-812b-3a1b7a461f24</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 15:14:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let It Go!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Let It Go!</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d42d8bfa-499c-471a-b08f-24b420c55957.jpg">,<p>If you're like me, you love to be in control. As a first born son, I was put in charge by my parents often. I was supposed to be the responsible child and watch over my younger brothers. At first, it didn't seem fair. As time went on I fell in love with being in control.</p>,<p>The problem with loving control is that life is messy. Just the other day I was trying to clean our ice maker. I read through the directions a couple of times and discovered that it was a very easy process. I followed the directions to the letter and it didn't work. The machine just beeped at me and asked for me to give it cleaner. I had already filled the machine with the required cleaner and water. Yet, it just beeped. I had lost control of the situation and then lost control of my emotions (my wife would say that included my mind).</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/let-it-go/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">713d8eb8-91f9-4ff3-a418-2d241d54ce7f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Witness!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Witness!</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8bce2f7b-8fc3-4ef1-8eeb-843a3c7089c5.jpg">,<p>I often think about&nbsp;<em>why</em>&nbsp;I am a Christian. I grew up going to church. But, so did a lot of my friends who are not Christians. I grew up in ‘Merica, but so did my friends who aren’t Christians. What happened in my life that led me to following Jesus?</p>,<p>As someone who holds to Reformed theology I know that my coming to faith, ultimately, was God’s work. He by his sovereign grace transferred me from the kingdom of darkness to the kingdom of his beloved son. I believe this and know this. But, what I ponder are the secondary causes that God used to bring about this change.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/witness/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">270f3643-118d-4eb2-ad99-a3fe444924b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 15:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Are You?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Who Are You?</h1>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/679b9928ea8a7415896e748d9328a8f6370b2f16.jpg">,<p>Today is Ash Wednesday. It’s the day that starts Lent and a traditional season of fasting. Have you ever wondered why the Church has done this leading up to Easter? It is partly due to preparation for Easter, the highest of all holy days. It is also due to the fact that, by and large, we know we need to come to a place where we once again recognize our need of grace.</p>,<p>We are a broken people. We are an imperfect people. We are a people in need of grace.</p>,<p>Do you want to be justified? Then you must recognize your need of grace.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/who-are-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4a35a293-30ba-47b2-ac64-bd1ff70dc067</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 15:43:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Jesus Way]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Jesus Way</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7a4d4657-90ab-4bbf-9ebf-2445de847e72.jpg">,<p>An insidious belief has exploded into American Christianity. This belief is that following Jesus will be all roses and puppies. Some call it the “Prosperity Gospel.” Its purveyors argue that if you have enough faith then you will have health and wealth. God wants you to be rich and that everything in your life should be going easy and well. </p>,<p>What an attractive offer! Who wouldn’t want that? </p>,<p>The problem is, that isn’t the Jesus way. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-jesus-way/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">184c9a66-b362-43f1-b2e1-4b173130494d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:20:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Lie</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8696f23d-b634-4adb-84c5-cc77698cf3b3.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-lie/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">22122e15-6d17-475f-b8c5-fd3ccad6952b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 18:47:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It Really Is About Jesus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>It Really Is About Jesus</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d4f47692-3b34-43c3-92cb-3ab8b25c9819.jpg">,<p>There is a constant refrain in our culture today, one that I have sometimes embraced, “Jesus, save me from your followers!” The Church has a bad rap because it is filled with broken people. We are all in process trying to be more like Jesus but we all fail, often. It gets really ugly when we “Jesus wash” our sinful behaviors. </p>,<p>The church functions in this world as Jesus representatives. It is completely fair for the world to, in some way, judge Jesus by the actions of the church. While it is fair, it is sad. It is sad because we fall so far short of who he is. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/it-really-is-about-jesus/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">42d1bca3-5083-49ac-b22f-3c2ce29f61db</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 15:10:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preach the Truth]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Preach the Truth</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c6365442-4316-4cfc-beb1-44b60b161f3a.jpg">,<p>In our social media world confirmation bias has become the air we breathe. If someone says something we don’t like we can “unfollow” or “unfriend.” It has become easier than ever to only hear, read, or interact with people who confirm our positions. We never need to interact with anyone who disagrees with us. Our positions or perspectives need not ever be challenged and we never need to be made to feel uncomfortable. </p>,<p>The church world is very competitive. Everyone wants to have a bigger and bigger church. Churches compete by having better facilities, cooler bands, and more dynamic programming. More and more they are finding that people will often leave when the preaching makes them feel “uncomfortable.” So, to remain competitive pastors are learning that they need to keep their sermons within a certain range of comfort to the hearers. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/preach-the-truth/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">628d6cb7-d6f9-468f-a009-7985aca16022</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 19:16:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[There’s More To It]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>There’s More To It</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/df93a531-2b6d-4670-bf17-b82613420547.jpg">,<p>One of the single hardest things about having teenage children is that they don’t see the bigger picture. They live completely in the moment and for the moment.</p>,<p>It drives me crazy!</p>,<p>We’ve all been there. It’s part of growing up. One of the hardest parts of being a parent is trying to teach your children to see more than the “now”. </p>,<p>Something the Christian has to come to grips with is not just that there’s more than the moment, but that there’s more than just this life. We must grapple with the reality of eternity.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/theres-more-to-it/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">100dcb5d-6916-47c3-b7fc-ed475545b9ba</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 18:23:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It’s Not A Sales Pitch]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>It’s Not A Sales Pitch</h1>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/9979ddb769e455aa01e61e0ebd66258e/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=3263&cropwidth=3871&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F5c957430-d5b9-4c48-bed9-b2a06d1aa93e.jpg&x=0&y=0">,<p>My Dad and Father-in-law are both car salesmen. My wife, Amy, and I both grew up appreciating salesmanship. The other day I had breakfast with my Dad and he told me about his new television. He was not planning on buying a television, he just wanted to go in and buy a rack that was capable of holding his 40” TV and a 65” TV whenever he upgraded.</p>,<p>The salesman went to work.</p>,<p>Dad appreciated the salesmanship (and the price!) so he bought at new 65” TV.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/its-not-a-sales-pitch/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">51e05fb6-1bc9-42a1-b1c8-8b276c6993a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 13:19:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>