<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rev]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rev]]></description>
        <link>http://danielmrose.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:43:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://danielmrose.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:43:19 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infinite Care]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Infinite Care</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/be4cbafa-9ffe-405d-92a5-fb6170331d82.jpg">,<p>There are times when we don't think God cares about us. For some of us, we think that we are so good off compared to others that God doesn't need to hear about our troubles.&nbsp;<strong>So, we hold them back from him.</strong>&nbsp;We think, "God has bigger things on his plate to worry about." Our world seems to be coming apart at the seams and our little issues don't appear to be that big.&nbsp;<strong>So, we hold them back from him.&nbsp;</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/infinite-care/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">13a35828-9857-4aba-9c96-55d2b8882708</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 18:14:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Just Me and Jesus…Nope.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Just Me and Jesus…Nope.</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/55672ef5-26d8-4665-9ae6-6f6df0835d1a.jpg">,<p>"Just me and Jesus." Have you heard that before? It's one of the single greatest lies that Christians have ever bought into.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/just-me-and-jesusnope/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ed73877-27da-4807-96e3-a291065d17a5</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 16:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Need to Engage]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>The Need to Engage</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0df21444-22b8-47c9-8c95-3561ad8f2754.jpg">,<p>Tuesday nights are my favorite night of the week. Hands down, it’s not even close. On Tuesday nights I gather with a group of people who were once strangers but have become friends. On Tuesday nights I hear some of craziest, most genuine, honest, authentic, and insane perspectives on the world. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/the-need-to-engage/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d25328c1-d18b-401a-a096-218816758f8e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 19:04:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selling The Church]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Selling The Church</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7e0280b5-f279-4691-a91c-b33acd0bd79f.jpg">,<p>One of my favorite authors is Eugene Peterson. He's a pastor's pastor. This man translated the Message while he was pastoring a local church. He has written extensively on what it means to be a pastor and what it means to be the church. One of my favorite quotes of his is this,</p>,<blockquote>The vocation of pastor has been replaced by the strategies of religious entrepreneurs with business plans.</blockquote>,<p>The church has, by and large, lost its way. It has become a place of commerce. Many of our church buildings look like malls. We work hard to figure out how to provide services for our consumers, I mean, congregants. The sad reality is that we are no different from those who have come before us. The Reformation came about, in part, because the Church was selling indulgences to help people get into heaven. But, even before that, the people of God mixed up their worship with commerce.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/selling-the-church/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03fa5510-561c-4b29-b0f7-ef8ed85f3014</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 14:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Never Forget]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Never Forget</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5e3240a9-4a4d-401a-89eb-a03d9b9da847.jpg">,<p>"Don't forget where you've come from." That's something that a lot of athletes say. Have you noticed that? Many of our greatest athletes come from unbelievably difficult circumstances. After they hit it big, many give back to where they came from. They don't want to forget their story and where they came from.</p>,<p>My story is like many others. I grew up in a single mother home. Mom worked multiple jobs to make ends meet. There were a number of years after my parents divorce where finances were in short supply. My Dad took care of big things for us, so we never missed out on school trips or playing sports. The day to day was different though. We just didn't have a lot. When I was in high school and college I felt ashamed of my story. I just wanted to forget it. I didn't want people to really know about it. But, as I have matured I have discovered that my story is a gift. It is a gift because through it God has shown me what redemption looks like. Through it I am able to meet so many more people where they are at in their lives.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/never-forget/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2f579a25-e50f-46e0-93c8-d16f12eff423</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 15:13:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Too Good to Be True]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Too Good to Be True</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/86791884-52a8-4b64-b470-dcecf4bcaa93.jpg">,<p>It was the summer after my junior year in college and I was working for my dad selling cars. During a sales meeting Marty, the sales manager said, “Remember, when you’re talking with a customer about some amazing deal from another dealer that if it’s too good to be true, it probably is.” Over and over again we find that to be a truism don’t we? People rarely under promise and over deliver. The fact is, if it’s too good to be true, it probably is. </p>,<p>Then there’s Jesus. </p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/too-good-to-be-true/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">76c28d72-b27e-466c-90ed-94672d4f3d2f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:26:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forgiveness is Blessing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Forgiveness is Blessing</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/30517ac4-b294-40f6-b28f-47b21bc30dc2.jpg">,<p>I will never forget the day. I was sixteen and had had my driver's license for a few weeks. It was one of those fall days in Michigan where the leaves had fallen and there was a thick dew. My family lived in a small neighborhood shaped like a horseshoe. On my way to school I was changing CDs and not paying attention. I looked up to see I was running out of road. I slammed on the brakes and turned the car. I had hit the wet leaves and slid into a few mailboxes. Looking around, I saw no one, so I backed out and hurried off to school.</p>,<p>After school, I was watching television and the phone rang. My stomach dropped. Somehow, I knew this was about the mailboxes. I heard the "Yes" and "OK" and "We will see you soon, officer." I was dead. Mom looked at me and asked if I had been a part of a "hit and run." I was caught and all I could do was say yes and tell her the story.</p>,<p>We went to the police station where I got a scolding and then I had to apologize to the neighbors. It was horrible.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/forgiveness-is-blessing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">52cc9a5e-572c-455c-812b-3a1b7a461f24</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 15:14:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let It Go!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Let It Go!</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/d42d8bfa-499c-471a-b08f-24b420c55957.jpg">,<p>If you're like me, you love to be in control. As a first born son, I was put in charge by my parents often. I was supposed to be the responsible child and watch over my younger brothers. At first, it didn't seem fair. As time went on I fell in love with being in control.</p>,<p>The problem with loving control is that life is messy. Just the other day I was trying to clean our ice maker. I read through the directions a couple of times and discovered that it was a very easy process. I followed the directions to the letter and it didn't work. The machine just beeped at me and asked for me to give it cleaner. I had already filled the machine with the required cleaner and water. Yet, it just beeped. I had lost control of the situation and then lost control of my emotions (my wife would say that included my mind).</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/let-it-go/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">713d8eb8-91f9-4ff3-a418-2d241d54ce7f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Witness!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Witness!</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8bce2f7b-8fc3-4ef1-8eeb-843a3c7089c5.jpg">,<p>I often think about&nbsp;<em>why</em>&nbsp;I am a Christian. I grew up going to church. But, so did a lot of my friends who are not Christians. I grew up in ‘Merica, but so did my friends who aren’t Christians. What happened in my life that led me to following Jesus?</p>,<p>As someone who holds to Reformed theology I know that my coming to faith, ultimately, was God’s work. He by his sovereign grace transferred me from the kingdom of darkness to the kingdom of his beloved son. I believe this and know this. But, what I ponder are the secondary causes that God used to bring about this change.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/witness/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">270f3643-118d-4eb2-ad99-a3fe444924b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 15:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Are You?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Who Are You?</h1>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/679b9928ea8a7415896e748d9328a8f6370b2f16.jpg">,<p>Today is Ash Wednesday. It’s the day that starts Lent and a traditional season of fasting. Have you ever wondered why the Church has done this leading up to Easter? It is partly due to preparation for Easter, the highest of all holy days. It is also due to the fact that, by and large, we know we need to come to a place where we once again recognize our need of grace.</p>,<p>We are a broken people. We are an imperfect people. We are a people in need of grace.</p>,<p>Do you want to be justified? Then you must recognize your need of grace.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://danielmrose.com/who-are-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4a35a293-30ba-47b2-ac64-bd1ff70dc067</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 15:43:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>